I think I think a lot of it is the fans.
I would say that. I mean, it's just like
I don't know what it is, but it's just
the
the atmosphere. It's hard to really
describe like just coming down here and
playing in the stadium as an opposing
team. It's it's just a hard place to
play in.
Ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls,
synchronize your watches. Look at your
calendars. We are now inside of 1 month
until the 2026
annual selection
meeting. It's also known as the NFL
draft. And welcome to another edition of
the best podcast available presented by
Bullseye Event Group. For award-winning
game day experiences, visit
bullseyeeventgroup.com.
Happy draft month. I guess we're inside
of a month give a to you and yours. I
can't go with that until after April 1.
April 1, I'm officially in the month of
the draft. I know we're inside a month,
but
April is the month of the draft.
>> There are multiple ways and I'm with you
to look at this. By the way, hi, I'm
Andrew Siciliano. That's Jason Gibbs.
Thanks for being here.
So I woke up on Monday morning of this
week, tore up my bracket cuz my bracket
was worthless, and I turned on the
social media and everything said it's 1
month until the draft and I'm like, wait
a minute. It is cuz the draft is on
Thursday, April 23rd in Pittsburgh,
Pennsylvania and this was Monday, March
23rd.
But the draft is on a Thursday. So when
when you say it's 1 month until the
draft, you could also on the Thursday
4 weeks before say that's 1 month until
the draft, right? That's how I view 1
month until the draft.
I still
let's get through March.
We're wrapping down.
This is the end of the main free agency
push.
Obviously there'll still be plenty of
signings throughout the league as we go
here, but
the bulk of free agency is almost in the
rearview mirror. We have the owners
meetings,
coach meetings, GM meetings. Anybody
who's anybody will be at the fantastic
Biltmore Hotel in Arizona
early next week and then and then we're
into April and then we're draft time,
baby.
>> Absolutely. And we will continue to
bring you the best podcast available all
the way up through and after the draft
as well. And we're excited to do that.
We're excited also bring you Taiwan
Wallace, the Browns new wide receiver, a
former Baltimore Raven, a guy who knows
Todd Monken from
Baltimore.
He will join the show coming up in a
matter of minutes. And you mentioned the
owners meetings. Technically, Give A,
it's called the annual meeting.
We will have content from the annual
meeting where
>> fancy names for things. You started off
with the name for the draft.
>> It's called the annual selection
meeting. That You know what that is?
That's election Sunday for me in March.
Like that's not Yeah. And and the owners
meetings, the league does push back.
They don't want them known as the owners
meetings. This is the annual meeting and
when there's a meeting say in season
owners meetings in season on the
network, you're you're to refer to that
as the fall meeting.
And I can understand the annual meeting
because like I said, you know, Todd
Monken will be there. There's a
breakfast with coaches. There's, you
know, GM talks. Andrew Berry will talk
to the media informally and formally. So
>> Monken will be there. He'll ownership.
Yeah. Ownership will speak.
Scheduled to speak. So all those things.
Yep. And we'll have that content for you
from Phoenix next week. All right, let's
get to the content right now. You said
free agency is wrapping up. Browns made
two special team signings that I think
are significant here. One of which,
Taiwan Wallace, we mentioned, will join
us coming up shortly. The other is
Daniel Thomas. He's a veteran safety
most recently with the Lions.
We We spent a lot of time last year
lamenting the Browns special teams
units. Obviously week one he got a lot
of headlines. Andre Szmyt missed the two
kicks and then turned it around and
turned it a fantastic season culminating
with that game-winning field goal week
18. Yes, and we're happy for him in
Cincinnati with that win over the
Bengals. But coverage was certainly an
issue. Returning was certainly an issue.
The Taiwan Wallace signing and the
Daniel Thomas signing I think go a long
way towards trying to fix those issues.
Annually it seems the Browns bring in a
return man.
It often doesn't work. Taiwan Wallace, I
think the the the layman may look at it
and go, oh, well, he's the returner.
He's always the Ravens fourth or fifth
wide receiver. He has a punt return
touchdown in his resume here in the NFL.
And I say, yes, but no. He has had
return success, but he has not really
been a return man, Give A. He has been a
guy that has excelled on coverage units.
He has over 1,000 career special team
snaps. And yes, he does have some
explosiveness in the return game and he
could be your fourth and fifth wide
receiver hoping to get a little bit more
of a bite of that apple as well. Yeah, I
This football team has been snakebitten
when it comes to signing free agent
return men who have a track record of
performing
and then
freak injuries. I don't even want to go
down the list.
I'm not going to jinx it and go down the
list. No, no, no, no, no. I No, we we
don't need to revisit it, but
you know, it it's been unfortunate for
both the player and for the franchise
because
probably Josh Cribbs is the last person
that struck fear in any team when it
comes to a return man.
>> Must See TV for the football team. Yeah.
And I don't think that we've had that in
quite a long time if we're talking about
him being the last real relevant
returner. Now, to be fair, he was more
than just a relevant returner. Josh
Cribbs, and you could go look at the
stats, go to Pro Football Reference, is
one of the most prolific return men in
the history of this game.
Period. Full stop. So it's a high bar.
And before him you had Eric Metcalf
obviously back in the good old days. So
the Browns have had their legendary
return man. That is a very high bar to
meet. You just would love to get kind of
1/3 of the way there. Correct. Yeah, and
that's we've seen flashes from guys over
the years and here's hoping that you
know, the gentleman that's going to join
you in a little bit, Mr. Wallace, is a
guy that can
maybe provide a little punch for that
special teams return group. I think we
thought about Josh Cribbs as a returner,
but Josh Cribbs could cover kicks and
punts
>> Absolutely. and do it exceptionally
well. And that's
you mentioned it.
It's not just the return game that has
struggled for this franchise. It's been
the coverage unit. We don't have to
revisit the Jets game from last year. We
did that last week with Quincy Williams.
That's right.
I think it's one of those situations
where the special teams unit needed an
overhaul and I think that there's a
number of reasons why special teams
struggled last year, but
I think having designated special teams
players,
guys that excelled that that really
thrive in special teams play
were not prevalent on this football team
a year ago. And I think there's been a
concerted effort this offseason to bring
in a couple guys to help out in that
aspect.
>> Absolutely. And really special teams I
think has been the focus of the past
week. It's not just Taiwan Wallace and
Daniel Thomas. I don't remember if we
got the Corey Bojorquez signing in when
we did last week's episode, but it
should be noted Corey Bojorquez, who
many people thought honestly was out the
door, Corey is back. It's a 1-year deal.
It's great to have him back just on and
off the field. Obviously he Nathan sat
down with him last week. Loved that
interview. He was on CBD.
Loved the guy. There are a lot of
factors last year I think
that went in
to Corey Bojorquez perhaps not having
statistically his best season. Hopefully
you can and we talked about coverage
here clean some of that stuff up and he
can get back to the guy who 2 years
previous was one of the best in the NFL
not only at A booming punts, but B
downing them inside both the 20 and the
10-yard line. So happy for Corey and
they have a baby, another one coming
soon. So happy for the entire Bojorquez
family.
>> I would say any day now.
>> Any day now. Yeah. As we sit here
recording this on a Tuesday.
A couple of other key special teams
signings, Trey Avery and D'Angelo Ross
are two corners. They're veteran corners
who the Browns picked up in season last
year because they needed help on special
teams. Guys that at times later in the
year were pressed on to the field and
they were needed defensively and took
some meaningful defensive snaps, but
were primarily teams guys. So they both
resigned as well. They provide veteran
depth in the cornerback room and they,
assuming they're there come week one,
provide core special teams value. So if
you look Taiwan Wallace, Daniel Thomas,
D'Angelo Ross, Trey Avery, and even to a
degree Sam Kamara, although he's a
rotational piece, can play both inside
and outside on that defensive line,
primarily inside.
Those guys all, as we get to the second
and even maybe now the third wave of
free agency, provide core teams value.
We're going to beat the dead horse here.
It [snorts] is a an essential part of
this game. Games were won and lost and
primarily lost, let's just call it like
it is last year, on special teams. You
cannot, as as much hand-wringing as we
have done this offseason over the
defensive coordinator position, you
cannot you cannot overemphasize the role
special teams played last year in the
win-loss record. All right.
It's 33% of your team.
You're good at math.
>> I I I I Well, public school kid, once in
a while I get one right. Right here. Um
it's 33% and I don't care you you can
come back and go, "It's really 20% and
like the other 13% should go to offense
and all that." All three phases, like
there's a reason why Gerod Cherry calls
it complimentary football. All three
phases have to perform for you to win on
a Sunday in the National Football
League. And Gerod, and that's why I love
having him on the sideline, obviously,
for a number of reasons, but last year,
um we could go down I mean, look every
year, every game, go down to Gerod and
his special teams analysis cuz that's
how he made his bones in his career,
especially later in his career,
um is invaluable.
Um what makes a good special teams
player?
Yeah, [snorts] it's alignment,
assignment, and effort, all of that, but
um
a lot of it is just effort. As Gerod
said repeatedly
last year, you know what? I'm going to
ask Tylen Wallace, what makes a good
special teams player?
Coming up shortly. Um
Mamoudi Diabate was also a good special
teams player. Let's get to him. Because
that one was a bit surprising. The
Browns chose not to tender him, meaning
you can [snorts] walk away without any
free agent compensation. Had to be fair,
the Browns would have not necessarily
gotten some massive free agent
compensation if Mou left, and he did. He
signed on with the Tennessee Titans, but
they get nothing because they did not
tender him. It also leaves a bit of a
hole. We mentioned Quincy Williams, he
signed, he takes Devin Bush's spot
there. The Browns really
are lacking right now, just in core
depth in the special teams room. Now,
you've got a couple of guys who showed
some promise in 2024 coming back,
hopefully better than ever from injury.
And that is Winston Reed, Winston, I beg
your pardon, Reed and Bookie Watson. We
never saw him last year. They were both
injured. But logic dictates that you
need to add more. Now,
we're not through the offseason,
friends. There is another wave of free
agency. There is an NFL draft, which is
significant. With the 33rd overall pick
last year, you found a pretty good
linebacker. And even though you don't
think the Browns may go offense at 6 and
24, you never know. So, the puzzle is
still very much being constructed. But
if you had to play a game today, which,
full stop, you don't,
Easton Mascarena-Arnold, who is a key
special teams contributor as a kid out
of USC last year, would be on the field
in all likelihood with that first team
defense.
Yeah, I we talked a little bit about it
on Monday's Cleveland Browns Daily. We
had Jason Tarver, the linebacker coach,
as we
>> Right out of the gate to start the show,
Jason Tarver. Kicked off the week with
the fact
>> enthusiasm. He couldn't even get the
name of the show out. He was like, "And
here's Jason Tarver." That's right.
That's exactly right. Might have been he
also was excited for vacation, but he
was also excited for Jason Tarver. Um
Coach Tarver's got his got his work cut
out for him.
I mean, this is a a position group that
I think going into the offseason, we
thought was in a good spot. And now,
well, I mean, that's you've got some new
faces and you're probably going to need
a few more new faces.
>> You're going to. Yeah, and that's I I'm
surprised they didn't tender Diabate
uh for whatever reason, and that that's
I'm not the GM and I don't make those
decisions, but I I think that was a
little surprising given how well he had
played, especially in special teams, but
maybe you needed a little bit of a
facelift in that area. And that's they
wanted to go in a different direction
and
you know, I I don't know the reason, but
we have to replace Mamoudi Diabate now
and uh you know, that that's just
another another spot on a defense that
you thought you weren't going to have to
do a lot of work with in the offseason
that all of a sudden, you've had to
replace some guys here. And now, that's
taken away from the, you know, the
salary cap situation on the offensive
side of the football. Absolutely. Uh
defensively, MJ Emerson is still out
there. I know Nathan's pounding the
table for him. I I will as well. Now,
you know, you may get some pushback from
Browns fans saying, "Hey, when last I
saw him in 2024, he was not having a
good year." No, he wasn't and and he
admits that. And it's part of what makes
his injury last year so heartbreaking.
If you guys want to go back to that day
in July, MJ had been on the podium
earlier that afternoon and he really
opened up about um the mental health
struggle of of of having a difficult
season in and how he worked so hard in
the offseason to put that behind him and
be a better him both on and off the
field. And there was a twinkle in his
eye and then there was like a a positive
outlook and and just extreme optimism
for the year to come. And then later
that day, he went out and he tore his
Achilles. He he was back in the building
pretty quickly, rehabbing, fighting. He
was around last year and all of us,
fingers crossed, were hoping he'd be
back. Not saying it's not going to
happen. It could still happen. Until he
signs somewhere else, I have reason to
be optimistic that it could happen.
Because I think, and listen, coming back
from an Achilles is never easy. For a
corner, it is especially difficult. All
the cutting and the backpedaling,
um it's not easy. It it's not He he's
got a battle to come back, but I believe
in the player, but more importantly, I
believe in MJ Emerson. So, fingers
crossed. If not, you're likely going to
add another veteran corner somewhere.
And I want fans to remember, and and
this is always Listen,
we're not playing fantasy. We want to
stack our roster right now. The first
game isn't until September. There will
be veterans that come free after June 1.
There will be veterans that come free
in training camp. There can be other
acquisitions,
um other means to stack your roster.
Just because you're looking at
linebacker or corner right now and
going, "We need help." Okay, fine. Yeah,
wide receiver, yep, I get it. Um the
offseason still has a lot of time. Yeah,
well, you
you ultimately, I think, want six or
seven corners
on your roster to get through the year,
to get through everything. And I think,
you know,
Trey Avery and De'Angelo Ross,
you know, they those are bodies that can
add things not just on defense, but on
special teams. So, you have that, but
then you also have the play of Tyson
Campbell, who the Browns went out and
had to get. And now, where does MJ
Emerson fit with Tyson Campbell and
Denzel Ward?
>> You need more than two. Only two can
play outside. Yeah, but only two can
play outside. I understand that. Myles
Harden's coming back as well. Yeah. Um
is MJ back?
>> MJ's not a good fit to play inside.
No, I get that. He he isn't. So, your
priority may be slot as opposed to
outside. You need more than two outside
corners. You do.
You you you simply do. The way this game
is played, the way the Bengals are going
to play this game,
the way, who knows what the Ravens are
going to look like this year,
obviously, you need more than two. We'll
see what happens.
The offseason is still quite young. And
the draft is a month away. We'll get
into 6 and 24 coming up in a second, but
for now, let's introduce you to a new
face in that wide receiver room.
We're going to keep this thing going
here with new Browns on BPA. We've had
on Titus Howard, we had on Quincy
Williams. Welcoming now to the show,
he's a wide receiver, he's a returner,
he's a man who does everything. He is
the newest Brown and he is live with us,
live on tape. What does it matter? It's
a podcast. Tylan Wallace, how the heck
are you, man? Yes, sir. I'm great. Good
to be here. How's it How's it feel going
Baltimore to Cleveland? This isn't like
going Baltimore to Denver, all right?
Baltimore to Arizona. It's Baltimore to
Cleveland, man. Yeah, keeping it in the
conference. So, no, I'm I feel good
about being here, though. I know some
people don't feel the same, but I'm I'm
happy to be here. Wait a minute, who
doesn't feel the same? Uh a couple of
Baltimore fans, but you know, it's all
right. It'll be all right. Have they
been blowing up your mentions?
A little bit. Maybe just a little bit,
but a lot of most of them positive, so
I'll say that. A lot of them were
positive.
>> Okay, so I'll ask you the same thing I
asked
Coach Monk and same thing I asked Travis
Switzer.
What are you doing with all your Ravens
gear?
>> [laughter]
>> That's a great one. I'm I'm going to
keep it for later on down the road, you
know, when I'm, you know, done playing
everything, I'll still have it and, you
know, I'll keep it in the in storage for
now. Okay, that's that's a good answer.
You're not just like dropping it out on
the curb and waiting for the Monday
pickup. You're not doing that.
>> No, definitely not. I can't do that.
Can't do that. Let's talk about Coach
Monk. How How much of an influence was
he in your decision? Yeah, all a big I
mean, obviously, big influence. Being
there with Monk, you know, I love being
there with him and how he ran the
offense and just uh how he held himself
just as a coach and how he treated
everybody in the in the building and not
only just the players. So, um you know,
it was great to be around Monk and it
was a big, you know, part of my decision
process to to come here.
We've We've seen him, obviously. We've
We've talked to him. He's at the podium.
He's done the interviews. He's been the
man around town.
What's he like in a meeting room? Like
when he's the OC, now he's head coach
obviously, but when he's the OC and he's
up there in front of the room, what's he
like?
He's great. I mean, he's he's a
personality, I'll give him that. He he's
definitely a
what do you call a a big personality
guy, but definitely love Monk, man. Love
being around him. Just love the way he
he holds himself and
it's something you got to experience to
be in a meeting room with that guy. Does
he call you out? Does he call you up? Is
he the teacher that like makes you stand
up and and recite your homework? Like
like like what are we doing?
He he's had those moments for sure where
he's one of those
I guess teachers that make you stand up
and say
make you stand on your word, I guess he
would say. So
he's one of those, but it's good for
everybody I think when he does that in
in a good way. It it's kind of like a
good-natured get in your face. He's not
a screamer, he's a I might make fun of
you.
Like am I on the right track here?
Exactly. Exactly. Yeah, definitely
definitely all in a good way, for sure.
You scored a touchdown last year week
two against the Browns in September. If
I had told you that day that you'd be
wearing the other uniform playing
against the Ravens next year, what would
you have thought? I wouldn't have
thought there was no no chance. I
wouldn't have thought about that, but
you know, it's
it's crazy how how everything ends up
coming full circle and I'm just I'm
really happy to be here. I was going
down a rabbit hole last night on the
internet. There's some Ravens content
where it it it pointed out how you
earlier in the game had gone in motion,
dug out Devin Bush and kind of set that
whole thing up. Take me through that.
Yeah, so going going into that game plan
that we kind of had that set up where
like you said bringing that same motion
in going you know, block the linebacker
and then play later. He's I guess you
know, Monk Monk being Monk dials it up,
calls the same play, but calls the pass
off of it.
I end up coming coming open in the back
of the end zone and Lamar throws it to
me for a touchdown.
How do you and I'm sure I'm sure this is
part of the conversation, but I don't
want to put words in your mouth and
assume. You had a thousand special teams
plays over the years, but you also had
that touchdown. You had the 84-yarder
against the Bengals which Ravens fans,
you know, still talk about to this day.
How do you whether it's a slot, a Z,
whatever, Tylan, get on the field more
on offense?
I think it's just taking advantage of
the opportunities. I feel like that's
kind of been my thing that I've always
taken pride in ever since I've been
playing was no matter when I'm on the
field, how often I'm on the field,
whenever I am on the field, is to take
advantage of whatever opportunities I do
get.
Does it get annoying sometimes when
people say, "Oh, he's a great special
teams player, he's a core special teams
guy." Which is important. It's very
important. We know that. It is
important. And and I'm guessing part of
you wants to be like, "Hey, like turn on
my college tape, man. Like I I lit it
up." You're right. Right. Yeah, for
sure. You know what I mean? Like I think
obviously I think in this league that's
what everybody looks for to have that
recognition as their
role as if it's a receiver, linebacker,
safety, you know what I mean? You want
that recognition as that position that
you play, but also like I said, I take a
lot of pride in playing special teams,
you know what I mean?
So no matter what it is, I just want to
be known as a great football player.
I'll take that any day. What makes, bear
with me here, we'll get back to the
offense. What makes a great special
teams player though, Tylan?
I think it's if you ask me, it's just a
lot of it is just effort. I mean, it's
just a lot of effort and unselfishness.
You got to be willing to run down there
and you know, sometimes you got
try to block 300-lb lineman at times if
you have to, you know what I mean? Just
being able to be unselfish and
block guys and and just make plays that,
you know, normally don't call for,
especially for me at the receiver
position, you know, we're not normally
used to making tackles or doing things
like that. So I think just having that
part of unselfishness and effort. See,
that's the thing when when people say
you're a core special teams guy, which
again can be a compliment, it's
definitely a compliment. People think
that well, you know, you're just that
return guy, you're the wide receiver,
you're not necessarily. That's not
always been part of your game. Matter of
fact, when you ran that punt back
against the Browns, I'm sorry, the Rams
in 2023,
that was your very first game ever
returning a punt in the NFL. Yep. Yep,
that's right. Yes, sir.
And that wasn't just like, "Hey, he ran
a punt back in the first quarter." I
mean, that was a game-deciding
play.
Yes, sir. Yeah, it was it was crazy how
that all even happened. Like you know,
I've been the you know, I was a backup
punt returner for
the longest obviously and then played
before that our starting turner Devin
Duvernay got hurt. So they were like,
"All right, Ty, you got to you know,
it's overtime, you got to go catch this
punt." And I was like,
and and at the time you know, it had a
little rain, little drizzle and
everything, so it wasn't like perfect
conditions either, but
I just knew when the only thing I had to
do was just go back there and catch it.
I said, "I can as long as I can do that,
you know, I can let Lamar do his thing."
But I guess you know, he never got the
chance to.
Did we get just you and me talking here
cuz I got some friends who are Rams
fans. Do you think Charlie Kohler
blocked Jake Hummel in the back there?
>> [laughter]
>> That's so funny you say that cuz they
talk they talk about that nonstop. You
know, that that year after that Jake
Hummel came over to us and he told
him I mean, he told he tells him about
that every day, every day we were there.
It was hilarious.
True story. And and they're boys, too,
those two guys. Like from back at home.
So
I was watching that play, full
disclosure, Tylan.
I'm watching that play as it happened
and I yell, "BLOCK IN THE BACK!" AND I'M
WAITING FOR THE FLAG, waiting for the
flag, waiting for the flag and they
just, you know, there's you celebrating
with your guys in the end zone, they cut
away to the crowd, the crowd's going
nuts. I'm like,
guess they're not throwing that flag.
Yep, I was I was very happy they didn't,
for sure. So what's it been like playing
at Huntington Bank Field over the years
when when you come to town? Last year's
a great game, tied tied at the wire,
obviously Shedor's got a shot at the
end.
Years past, you had Jameis
you know, throwing the touchdown pass
late to win it. What are your what are
your thoughts, your memories on the
building?
So the the crazy thing obviously me and
the Ravens like playing here, we haven't
had super great memories playing here,
but
you know, I've always enjoyed the the
atmosphere here, you know what I mean?
It's it's real different. I feel like
it's a it's it's a harder place to play
in than people I think try to than what
they would say, but you know, I've loved
the atmosphere here, the the crowd when
they show up. I mean, it's it's really
just
an atmosphere that I'm like, "Okay, I
can I can rock with this." It's it's
been a point of frustration, too, for
the Ravens over the years a little bit.
Why do you think it is? Other than it is
it just the fans? Like cuz the Steelers
obviously haven't had success recently
in Cleveland either.
I think I think a lot of it is the fans.
I will say that. I mean, it's just like
I don't know what it is, but it's just
the
atmosphere. It's hard to really
describe. Like just coming down here and
playing in the stadium as a an opposing
team, it's it's just a hard place to
play in.
Well, now you're going to be part of
that atmosphere. Do you have a number
yet? You met with Corey yet?
Yeah, I think we're still working on it.
We had the talks about possibly number
15, but we're we're still hashing some
things out to make sure. Okay, so Isaiah
Likely got 16, you've worn 16. Remind me
what you wore in college. Two.
Two.
Okay.
Does 15 feel right? If it is 15, For
sure. For sure. All right. Want to tell
a little bit of your backstory here
before we get you out of here. Those who
don't know, you have an identical twin.
Right? Like identical. Like can people
tell you and Tylan apart if you're both
in the same room?
I think now now they can. Just just for
the fact that we have different haircuts
and things like that now, but back then,
I don't think so. No. And you guys were
like these amazing recruits, played
together, he was a quarterback, you were
wide receiver. He had a couple of bad
knee injuries in high school, you guys
both went to Oklahoma State together and
then he had another injury and he had to
shut it down, but he's now in coaching.
He was at Oklahoma State, now he has
moved on to Butler. Tell me about his
career and and
I look, I have to assume identical
twins, you guys are like this. Do you
feel at times like you're playing for
him?
Always. Always. I mean, that was always
the goal. Once he, you know, went
through what he went through and he
obviously couldn't play anymore, I think
that was always part of my motivation
why I kept going and why I kept playing
was to to play for him and you know,
kind of play for both of us.
Yeah, him tearing his ACL two times in
high school, one time in college,
obviously he had to take the the
coaching route.
And you know, I know that wasn't easy
for him, so I always try to anytime I
step on the field, always try to make
sure I'm putting my best foot forward
for the both of us.
How good could he have been?
I think honestly he would have been
right up here with me if you ask me.
I mean, I think if you turn on our high
school tape, it I mean, it shows it all.
I mean, he had all the talent that I did
and I think with without the injuries,
he'd be in the same position I'm in
right now.
Does he call you up? Cuz he's coaching
wide receivers, too.
Does does he call you up and break down
your film on Sunday night?
So he does sometimes. So yeah, if he
sees something on TV, he sees it, he'll
he'll call me up and be like, "Hey, you
know, I saw this." Or you know what I
mean? "What were you what were you
thinking on this?" Or things like that.
Or I'll even send him sometimes like
some practice tape and he'll try to
coach me up through things on what he
sees and what he would have said or
something like that. So you never you
never hit him back and go, "Dude, you're
a quarterback. Like stop it.
>> [laughter]
>> I know what I'm doing." No, I I try I
try to make him, you know, yeah, I know
he knows what he's talking about. So
I'll I'll let him have it. I'll take the
coaching points.
That's cool. Tylan, we appreciate your
time. I know you're kissing babies and
shaking hands today. Welcome to
Northeast Ohio. Can't wait to see you
back out there on the field wearing an
orange helmet this time regardless of
which number we settle on. Welcome to
Cleveland, man.
>> Thank you. I appreciate it. Looking
forward to it. Tylan Wallace.
Nice guy. And
Gibby, he and I both had this epiphany
as he was sitting down that when he was
coming out of college
I interviewed him on NFL Network. Same
setup. I don't know that I've ever met
the guy. I'm on one camera, he's on
another camera, different rooms,
different states, whatever. He's like,
"Oh, yeah."
I remember you. Yeah.
Yeah.
>> And I hope it all works out. Like that's
for the for the team, for him, for
everyone involved. Want him want him to
be successful. Absolutely. And he does
have some explosive in his bag. Go look
at that punt return. Go look um go look
at the the the play against the Bengals
where he broke free down the sideline.
And yes, he caught the week two
touchdown last year in Baltimore um
against the Browns. All right. Gibby, we
got some mailbag questions.
>> We do. All right.
You want me to You want me to ask you or
are you asking
>> you. Oh god. Here we go. Buckle up.
Browns have six and 24 as we sit here
today in round number one. Do they Gibby
pick two wide receivers on Thursday,
April 23rd?
>> No. I would like them to, but probably
not. I think you
I personally would go wide receiver at
six because maybe the guy I want that I
think will fall to 24 might not fall.
So, if you love a guy and he's a wide
receiver
take him at six and alleviate the prob-
problem. And then
And if you go offensive lineman at 24,
I'm fine with that as well. Okay. So,
this is called the best pod available,
best podcast available. Obviously, it's
a play on best player
available. And that is what you have to
do. You have to take the best player
available. And I I have said repeatedly
that the difference between the wide
receiver you can get at six and 24 is
far greater than the difference I'm
sorry is is is
the difference between the old lineman
you can get at 24 as compared to six
is far different than the wide receiver
you can get at 24 as compared to six.
Easier said, there is far more depth at
wide receiver in this draft than there
is at offensive line. There's going to
be a run at offensive lineman early.
There could be a run at wide receivers
early as well. If you want an offensive
lineman, I think you have to take him at
six. Doesn't mean you the Browns can't
turn in 107 later and get a good
offensive lineman that turns into a
long-term starter. Of course, you can.
But in terms of blue-chip quality
guys, you may see 10. You might see a
dozen wide receivers taken in the first
two rounds. There are that many wide
receivers. Now
you keep hearing well, there's no
Ja'Marr Chase in this draft. No, there
isn't in all likelihood. There probably
is not.
Um but there is depth in the wide
receiver class. It's just I want you
guys to keep that in mind when you I
don't want an offensive lineman at six.
If I told I I'm fine with that. I
totally understand.
I just
if you get to number six and on your on
Andrew Berry's big board, not positional
by position, but on the big board
the wide receiver's higher than any of
the offensive lineman that are left, go
get him. If he's the best player, I'm
with you. Go get him. Go get him. Oh, by
the way, Ohio State pro day coming up on
Wednesday as we record this on Tuesday.
Uh we'll have some thoughts on that
coming up in next week's episode. It is
officially pro day season. Reuben Bain
on Monday did not have his arms measured
if you're concerned. It is silly season.
It is pro day season. Could any team be
looking to trade up at pick six, Gibby,
depending on how the board falls? I know
what I think. What do you think? I don't
think so. I think the answer is yes,
actually. Oh.
>> Yeah. So, here's
>> know. I I don't feel good about a trade
partner today as mid mid-week. Here's
what the Browns need.
The Browns need
Jeremiah Love to fall to six.
Browns fans
that is what you should be rooting for.
Have Jeremiah Love fall to six. Why? But
then we're moving back. I don't know if
I like that. Hold on.
There is nothing wrong with moving back
just an itty-bitty bit
if Okay. there is panic from the teams
below you
that Jeremiah Love may be taken by
somebody else, whether that is
Washington right behind you whether
that's New Orleans or Kansas City or
whomever. Oh, I know New Orleans Kansas
City went out and signed a back and
spent money in free agency. I know that
and that was a bit disheartening. I did
not want Travis Etienne
to go to New Orleans.
>> I did not want Kenneth Walker to go to
Kansas City. I wanted those teams to be
in prime we need a running back mode.
Neither is, but if you look at those
deals in reality, those are two-year
guarantees.
If you think Jeremiah Love is the best
player on the board and there are people
that have Jeremiah Love as the best
player in this draft.
Period. Full stop. You want him to fall
to six.
I know you're looking at me going, "I
don't want to trade back." Okay, fine.
But what if
what if hypothetically
say Washington's convinced that
someone's trying to get up ahead of them
to six to the Browns spot and Washington
will
flip you a three or four
to go back one spot when you know
they're taking Jeremiah Love. Go ahead.
That's free money. That third or fourth
round pick is a starter.
That fills out your roster
for nothing.
I
I'm fine if you're going to move back if
you stay in the top 10. Oh, yeah. I
don't want to move I don't want to move
out of the top 10.
>> want to go down there. I don't want to
move out of the top 10. Now, hold on.
Would you move out of the top 10 for
next year's one?
Yeah, but no one's giving you one. No
one's going to give you next year's one.
Exactly, Gibby. You passed the test.
Thank you. Thank you.
>> Yeah, no one no one's giving up ones in
2027. That is correct.
>> year's draft is next year's draft.
>> prediction.
There's my prediction. Nobody will give
up a one this entire draft in 2027.
I'm going to throw a caveat in there.
The only caveat is
if it's like the Seahawks, someone like
that where they have this overconfidence
or the Rams for that matter, though
highly unlikely with Stafford's
quarterback thing, with Stafford's
contract hanging out there.
Like a team that is absolutely all in
for this year and thinks that that one
is going to be 30, 31, or 32.
It's the only way.
The only way. That's right. Okay.
Gentlemen, that's been another edition
and ladies for that matter
of the best podcast available presented
by Bulls Eye Event Group. For
award-winning game day experiences,
visit bullseye eventgroup.com.
Give me any final thoughts. Get your
sunscreen ready, buddy.
I know you I know you live on the beach
now already, but yeah, you're going to
Phoenix. I don't live on the beach.
Okay, you live close to the beach.
Talking on the beach. I I spend my
off-season with you. I spend
my off-season
in a town that has beach
that has a beach nearby. That's I didn't
say you
but I watch you take a walk on the
beach, but
yet I would tell you like bring the
sunscreen. Okay. I think Phoenix the the
the desert sun and [snorts] heat a
little bit a little bit rougher than the
Southern California.
>> and you know why it's so hot there? Tell
me.
Chase DeLauter.
>> [laughter]
>> And now I need a drink.
On that note What a poll. we will be
back with another episode next week with
insight and content
from the annual meeting in the
aforementioned Phoenix, Arizona. For
Jason Gibbs, I'm Andrew Siciliano. So
long, everybody.